Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Why do you do all this?
There's no other way.
For what?
BHAMRAGAD POLICE STATION,
GADCHIROLI DISTRICT
Freedom.
Freedom! From whom?
From you and your masters.
Oh, so you want freedom from the country?
Only you and your master
do not make up the country.
We do, too.
So we want freedom
not from the country,
but from people like you.
So you think you can get freedom
by taking up arms
and killing innocents in your jungle?
Sardar…
You think the jungle is my home, right?
So here's a rule of the jungle.
You're either the hunter...
Or the hunted.
Long time ago,
there was a very hungry lion.
Whenever he would go on a hunt,
the prey would run away.
So he asked a goat and a dog for help
and all three of them
finally caught a prey.
The lion asked the goat to divide
the catch into three equal parts.
The goat did the same with fine precision
and presented it to the lion.
The lion turned red with anger
and devoured the goat.
Then, he turned to the dog and said…
"Now you divide the catch
into two equal halves. "
The dog immediately turned over
the whole catch to the lion
and started gnawing
at the bones of the goat.
The lion's eyes welled up
with tears of joy.
He said in an overwhelmed voice…
"It is rightly said!"
"No one can beat a dog at loyalty. "
Do you get it, Sardar?
We are the proverbial goat.
You are the dog.
And the lion is your master.
Hey, Sardar!
What the…
A blanket, cigarette…
What's all this?
Getting naughty under the sheets?
Feeling sorry…
Feeling sorry for her?
Son of a gun.
You bloody…
Take this off! Motherfucker…
Boss.
Want a go at her?
No…
I'll rot if I touch her.
-Boss! Come.
-Sir…
-Boss.
This isn't right.
This isn't right, sir.
Motherfucker, you want to teach me
what's wrong and right?
You want to teach me?
Fucker…
You bloody!
I'll take her.
Rotten works for me!
Tie her up!
Freedom!
From starvation, from cruelty,
The dying peasants ask for freedom!
Freedom!
From tyranny, this doomed life,
The unjust law
They ask for freedom!
Freedom!
-We'll fight for…
-Freedom!
-We'll die for…
We'll snatch our freedom
If we don't get it!
Freedom!
Shankar!
Long live the revolution!
Leave him.
Bomb…
If you ever want liberation
from oppression, use this.
THERE IS ONLY ONE GOD
How much does Surti pay?
Surti? No, Boss, you're mistaken.
We don't work for Surti.
Why is his coke cheaper
than mine in the market?
Boss, I don't drink Pepsi
nor do I make Coke…
How would I know?
Neither Pepsi nor Coke?
No, Boss.
Fanta?
Gold Spot? Mangola?
Double-seven?
-No, Boss.
-What else do you make?
A jackass?
Boss… Why would we lie to you?
Boss, Boss, Boss…
Lower the guns.
Boss, please tell them
to put the guns away!
Lower the guns. Let's talk.
Please, Boss!
Where do the Nigerians
get their coke from?
Nairobi… They get it from Nairobi.
How?
By hiding it up their ass.
Yes.
What's your share every month?
Boss…
No, Boss.
Okay, Boss, I'll tell you.
Boss, Boss… Rs. 2,00,000!
We get Rs. 2,00,000 every month, Boss.
Sir, you told me you get Rs. 1,00,000.
Paaji!
The fucker is lying.
He actually gets paid Rs. 3,00,000.
No. Last month, he gave me Rs. 3 lakh.
It was Rs. 2 lakh before that.
What do we do with him?
Shoot him.
No, Boss! Boss!
Boss, please don't kill me…
Boss, I swear! I'll do as you say.
Boss, Boss…
Are you up for sale?
Sold!
For how much?
Surti didn't just screw my business,
but my reputation too.
I'll pay whatever you ask for,
to kill him.
Ah! Thank you, Surti.
Have this.
Try it.
Delicious.
What's it called?
Khandvi…
Khand--
-Vi… Khandvi!
-Khandvi… Makes sense.
-It's a Gujarati roll, you know?
-Got it.
Paaji, listen.
I'll take down Surti and the blacks.
You bump off the rest.
Sir, can I take down Surti?
Why?
Over the last five years,
he's made me eat so much shit
that my stomach has almost become
a mine for oil and natural gas.
He has left me
with permanent acidity, sir.
I'll be the one to kill him.
-Phoolwadi… Flower.
-Can I try it?
-Good, no?
-It's all veg right? No meat?
There is meat.
There.
Hey, people!
-Let's go, sir?
-It's not twelve yet.
What will happen at twelve?
I have to break my fast.
It's a Tuesday.
Wait…
-Shall we, Paaji?
-Yes.
Gopal, are you alright?
Well…
Stray dogs are astray!
A bite here, a bark there!
Pounce at whatever comes their way!
Stray dogs are astray!
Don't kill me, man.
I saved your life! Please!
My gun…
Bring it. Fast!
Fast.
Please, come on, man.
Okay. Come on, man, please…
Look, look, you can have whatever…
You can take the drugs if you want.
Sir, let's not get involved
in this shit…
Are you crazy?
Should we just leave the stuff
worth two crores?
We're already getting two
for killing Surti.
So? Is there a problem
if we make two more?
If we leave the drugs here,
everyone will think the deal between
Surti and the Nigerians went wrong,
and that a shootout ensued.
Everything will be clean, sir.
Please, listen to me.
And what about him?
Kill him.
What is he saying?
He is asking me to kill you.
What the fuck? Why?
What did I do to you?
Sir, what are you doing?
-Paaji, why would you want me killed?
-No!
Listen, please…
Sir, if we spare him, we'll get screwed.
-I'll take the first flight out of India.
-No way!
Okay, look, I promise
I'll be on my first flight out of India.
Sir, if we spare him we're screwed.
-Please, sir.
-Sir, shoot!
Hey, let go of me!
Let go!
Look, Paaji, I did what you asked.
So now you will have to do what I ask.
Pick up the bags.
-Sir…
-Pick it up before I shoot you!
How long will you stay upset,
my millionaire friend?
Smile a little.
Didn't you learn how to swim
while training, sir?
Swimming? No.
I learned how to soar.
ID, please.
Cunning eyes
Your cunning eyes
Like shards of glass…
Cunning eyes…
I can understand why he did it.
But you've spent your whole life
on the force, Paaji.
Yet you did something like this?
Sir, we were undercover there.
Oh, is it!
Who assigned you this undercover job?
Your DCP?
The Commissioner?
The Home Secretary?
Or the Chief Minister himself?
Sir, the matter was a little sensitive
so we didn't tell anyone.
I'm telling you the truth, sir.
Lad, the truth is that
we found drugs in your car.
You took money
for the hit on Surti, right?
-Come on…
-Should I also reveal
who ordered the hit?
No, sir. This wasn't a hit…
Thanks to your shitty luck,
Surti took four bullets
and fell off the roof
but still survived.
Just pray that he doesn't come out
of the coma.
Otherwise, you'll lose your heads
along with your jobs.
Did you get the money yet?
This is what happens
when you try to ride two horses at once.
Paaji!
Manohar! What are you doing here?
I am his driver nowadays.
I heard about your suspension.
Remember Ms. Pammi?
-Poonam Sandhu…
-Yes.
She's the Commissioner's
favorite these days.
She's posted in Navi Mumbai.
She handles all of his dealings too.
See you.
Early morning,
chilly as hell…
Remember?
The living room was empty…
The bedroom was empty, too.
We thought he had run away.
But just then I heard a loud noise
from the toilet.
The door was unlocked.
I opened it and there he was, reading
a newspaper sitting on the toilet.
Just as he tried to get up,
I pumped three slugs into him…
Bang! Bang! Bang!
He sat back down on the toilet.
And then, his soul left his body
through his ass
towards the Grim Reaper, screaming…
Correct.
Those were the days, Paaji! Such fun!
These are the days, too, Ms. Pammi,
to slog.
But the thrill of being
a police inspector is gone now.
Now I've got responsibilities.
I mean…
Are you married yet?
Marriage?
Nice example.
So, are you?
No, Paaji.
The One above has stopped
making men lately, Paaji.
Now it's just small dumb fucks,
big dumb fucks,
or mega dumb fucks
that He sends into the world.
If a lion is thirsty…
It won't fucking drink poison, right?
Mr. Madam, we went to see Mr. Rajiv
a few days ago.
He was saying there's no hope.
Think of him as a newlywed.
He thinks he'll be faithful
to his wife forever.
I've spoken to the higher-ups.
Your issue can be sorted.
How much will it cost?
There is but one God.
One? For both?
No.
One for one, two for two…
Who is that?
Fucker, there's a public toilet
ten feet away!
Can't you see?
No! But I can smell it
from ten miles away.
Shut up and get out of here.
Am I pissing in your van?
Mr. Madam…
-What did you say? Son of a--
-Why you…
Harry!
-Pammi!
-Hey!
-At least wash your hands!
-It's clean.
-After all these years!
-Right, Harry.
Come, let's have a drink
for old times' sake.
No way, I'm on duty right now.
So do I look like I'm here on vacation?
-Come on.
-I've got company in the van.
Think of it as a dinner break.
We'll order some food for them too.
-You won't listen.
-Hey, Ramesh!
Come here.
-How many in the van?
-Four.
Send some chicken starters and Biryani
for the folks in that van.
You haven't changed at all.
-Come on.
-Okay.
Come on.
You haven't changed one bit.
-Nice, right?
-I know.
This is Paaji… My old colleague.
And this is Murli.
-It's Gopal, Mr. Madam. Gopal Tiwari…
-Gopal.
Gopal. Sorry.
Both are suspended right now.
-Really?
-Yes.
And this, the apple of my eye, Harry.
Harry.
He was on the force,
retired two years ago.
And what he does now,
even I don't know.
Oh, it's nothing.
-I'm into private security.
-Hmm?
For this company called Transecure.
That bank company?
We handle ATM deliveries for them.
How's the salary?
Way better than the force.
And the risk?
An automatic for a few lakhs?
Not lakhs, it's crores!
We load cash in all the ATMs
from Chembur to Panvel.
Every night.
-God.
-Sleepless and tired.
-Right.
-Leave it.
Tell me a joke.
-That Goa one?
-No. Something new. Fresh.
Okay. Here's a fresh and hot one.
One river, two lovers…
-One river, two lovers…
-Nice.
The male scorpion on one side
and the female on the other.
-Now how would they unite?
-Okay…
And then, the male scorpion saw a frog
on his side.
-Okay.
-He requested the frog,
"Please take me to the other side,
I'll forever be grateful. "
The frog hesitated a bit
and asked,
"What if you sting me on the way?"
-Correct.
-Isn't it?
The scorpion burst out laughing,
and said, "Are you crazy?
Use some logic.
If I sting you,
then I'll drown along with you!"
-Correct.
-"I'm begging you, please take me
or my Juliet will give up on me. "
The frog felt bad for the scorpion.
He let the scorpion climb on his back
and jumped into the river.
They must've reached halfway
when the frog felt like someone had put
a burning hot rocket up his ass.
First, the hot and heavy venom
of the scorpion…
And then, the cold intoxication of death.
The frog was left astounded.
With his last breath he asked,
"What is the logic behind this, pal?"
The scorpion muttered back
and said…
"Fuck the logic,
this is my character!"
My character…
His character!
Character…
What? Fuck the character?
Right!
-No, no! Fuck the logic.
-Fuck the logic!
-I said character!
-Right!
The scorpion got screwed.
Sorry… The frog!
-Character…
-His character.
-Fuck the logic.
Sir!
Mr. Gopal!
Sir, how do I manage one crore?
Do I look like Google
that you're asking for suggestions?
Do something…
Shoot yourself in the head.
Everything will be sorted.
Sir, I told you to leave the drugs.
But you didn't listen.
If I go down, I'll take you with me.
What did you say?
I will become a government witness!
Are you threatening me?
If I want,
I can pin the whole thing on you!
The whole station is with me.
One signal and they will testify
against you in court.
Asshole.
Pull over.
-Vivek!
-Say it again, asshole!
Vivek! Vivek…
Is this what you learn in school?
What will you do when you grow up?
Become a gangster?
Have you no shame!
Fighting on the streets like a stray dog!
I didn't start the fight, Dad!
I've been tolerating it for a while.
But today, I couldn't.
He said, "Your dad will get fired
from his job.
So sell this medal
before the government takes it back. "
Is this a reason to pick fights? Huh?
Dad, are you really going
to lose your job?
Have you lost your mind?
Why would I lose my job?
Silly boy!
Whatever we get above one crore
will be split equally between you all.
Mr. Gopal, I'll do anything for you.
I mean it!
What?
-What the fuck are you thinking about?
-Yes, sweetie?
-Papa, where are you?
-I'm at work. I'll be home late.
-Go to bed, okay?
-No, not until you sing me a lullaby.
Forgot about the Kurla encounter?
-If it weren't for Mr. Gopal…
-Okay, fine.
…you would've been hanged
for that kid's murder.
-Twinkle, twinkle, little star!
-Motherfucker! Speak up.
How I wonder what you are…
Sorry, Mr. Gopal. I am with you.
-Like a diamond in the sky!
-Sir…
Yay! Goodnight, Papa!
Goodnight, sweetheart!
Sir, we can't use our weapons or bullets.
Then how do we pull this off?
Everything's been arranged.
It's in the jeep.
There is at least four crores in the van.
Do I need to tell you separately?
Should I give it in writing now?
We said we are in.
With his last breath he asked…
What is the logic behind this, pal?
The scorpion muttered back…
Fuck the logic, this is my character!
Logic…
Isn't that Gopal?
Who? The one who's waving?
Wasn't he suspended?
Yes, that's Gopal.
Keep the engine running.
Gopal!
What's the matter?
Is Pammi with you?
Oh, fuck!
Motherfucker!
Sir! Sir! It has caught fire!
Run! Run!
Go! Run away!
Listen to me!
What are you doing?
No, no, not that way!
What are you looking at?
You won't get away, mother--
-Sir! Sir! Sir, please…
-Open it.
Sir, I only have one key.
The other one is with Samar.
-Samar who?
-The one who just ran out.
Deshpande, go check!
Please don't kill me, sir,
I have two younger siblings…
My family needs me, sir.
Sir, please!
Shut up!
I said shut up.
Get down!
Deshpande!
-No, sir.
-Fuck! Deshpande!
Sir, please!
They're from the bloody streets!
They pounce and they bark!
Dogs!
Stop! Stop, please!
Stop, mister! Please!
Stop, please!
Please! Stop, mister!
Get off!
Move! Move!
Get lost, asshole!
Stop, please…
Hey! Stop! Stop!
Stop crying! He's still alive!
Pal, let's just leave!
Samar! Listen! Samar…
If we spare him, we're doomed.
Sorry, sir! I screwed up.
I'm not doing anything. Please, sir!
Don't shoot me, sir.
Shut up!
Don't kill me, please.
Get up.
Get inside.
Hello! Some fuckers ambushed us
and stole the van!
They're heading towards you! Stop them!
Stop them, I'm coming as well!
Stop them!
Two kilometers from here,
you'll see a dirt road on the right.
Sir, you won't kill me, right?
No.
Promise me.
Once we reach the location,
I'll take the money and we all go home.
LET'S GO TO CANADA?
Boss, Gopal is here.
The sub-inspector.
We attacked them, Boss.
We even killed ten of his men.
But the one you were supposed to kill
is still alive.
His luck was good, Boss,
and ours was bad.
I'm screwed from all sides.
I didn't get paid for the hit
and I also got suspended.
You also made us look like fools.
What about that?
I'll be fired, Boss.
I might go to jail, too.
If they torture me in there
and I spill the beans…
Are you threatening us, asshole?
No.
I'm asking for help!
What do you want?
One crore.
I've not come to ask for money.
I'll arrange that.
I just need some weapons and bullets.
-Dad!
-Hmm.
Oh, my kitten!
Where are you going all dressed up?
Vashi. It's my friend's birthday.
Vashi? At this hour?
Yeah! That big-shot designer
will be there as well.
I'll speak to him about
my wedding dress, too.
What time will you come back?
I'll stay over at my friend's.
No! You're getting married
in two weeks.
So?
Dad?
Okay, fine. Go.
But Daanish will go with you.
Boss, I have a meeting in my--
He'll stay there as well.
Sleep in the car,
and drive her back in the morning.
Okay.
Love you.
-Meow!
-Meow.
Come on, Danny, quick!
It'll take two hours to reach Vashi.
It will benefit you
if I stay on the job, Boss.
Where in Vashi do you want to go?
I don't know.
What do you mean?
I mean, I don't know!
Stop screwing around, Lovely.
Tell me where you want to go.
Let's run away?
Are you deaf, bastard!
Do your lovey-dovey antics at home!
Lovely, don't do it.
I'll get lovey-dovey with your dad!
Take me to your house!
Lovely!
-Lovely, what--
-Scared little bitch!
Sit down.
Are you crazy?
I'm Khobre's daughter.
Lower it.
Now listen, what you did right now--
Lovely…
Stop. Stop it.
I said stop it!
Lovely, show it to me.
I feel suffocated at home…
Since my childhood.
I just wanted an ordinary life.
To be able to walk on the streets,
travel by bus, the local train…
Alone.
You know, till date,
none of my friends have fought with me
or teased me or scolded me or defeated me.
Just…
But everyone treated me like a queen…
I could see the fear in their eyes…
Always.
All my life,
I've been stuck with the name Khobre
like a curse…
What did I want from life, Danny?
Love, right?
And what did I get?
The builder's son!
I want to live with you
Won't you die with me?
As the rains pour
And the clouds roar,
Stay with me
On those dark nights,
Make me laugh so hard
That my tears trickle down my cheeks
I want to live with you
Won't you die with me?
Let's cross the tunnel
Into our next life
A moment where
We melt away in each other's arms
Let's fulfill our desire to live
This way, if we have to…
Why don't we run away!
Once we get married,
everyone will accept it.
Accept it!
To make the servant their groom,
instead of the builder's son!
Do you know what he'd do to me?
We can start a new life with new names…
Somewhere far away from here!
They will find us one way or another.
There's no way to escape
them in this country.
And outside the country?
Where will we go?
London, America?
Canada.
Aalaap called you?
No… Rasika did.
She said Aalaap offered it to you as well…
What?
They have a lot of contacts
in the government there, Danny…
They can easily get
our permanent residency visa.
Then he must have also told you
how much money they'll take!
One crore rupees!
Where would we get such a sum?
We'll get it!
-Where will we get it?
-We'll get it!
And until we get it, we can hide here.
Kerala, Tamil Nadu,
Manipur, Assam, anywhere!
Look…
Without you,
my life is like death.
But the truth is,
we won't die without each other.
We'll have to learn to live
without each other.
You learn!
I'm going to blow my brains out
on the wedding night.
Twinkle, twinkle, little star…
Forgot about the Kurla encounter?
If Mr. Gopal wasn't there,
you would have been hanged
for that kid's murder, motherfucker.
Sorry, Mr. Gopal, I am with you.
There is at least
four crores in that van…
Do I need to tell you separately?
Should I give it in writing now?
I look 'em dead in the eyes
When I tell them there's certain things
For which I'm ready to die
The money, the pride, the glory,
The life, we test fate
Bring guns to the fight
But then carry knives just in case
Who you place your trust in?
Who you know gon' stay solid
When enemies bust in, huh?
Keep the circle tight,
Nothing's what it seems
Nightmares every night
When you chase the dream
What are you chasing now?
They're stopping.
Danny, there's nothing here…
Get down.
What happened?
Down… down…
Danny.
What?
What is going on?
What are you doing, Danny?
God has answered your prayers.
Do you know how much money
is in that van?
So much… That forget Canada,
we can go to any country in the world!
Lovely…
Listen…
Hide behind that rock…
I'll be back before you know it.
No…
There's no time, Lovely… Go!
Get inside.
I won't let you go alone!
-It's too dangerous!
-That's why I'm saying it.
I want to live with you.
Won't you die with me?
Come on.
What are you doing, Danny?
He will be the one to get screwed
for the robbery.
Lovely, come here.
Give me a hand.
Come on.
What do we do?
We have to take this van…
Let's put him in our car
and blow it up.
Come on. Let's go.
Come on.
Grab his hand.
This way.
Come on.
Run!
Fucking hell!
Yeah!
Go check the back.
Did you find the key?
I'm checking, one second…
PEANUTS
Get off.
Get lost.
Go away.
Paaji! You're still awake?
Yes, Mr. Madam.
Listen…
Your friends are here with me…
Talk to them.
Hello, Paaji!
It's me, Jehangir.
Paaji, we're in big trouble.
You're the only one who can save us.
I beg of you… Please help us!
Paaji, a-are you listening?
Paaji--
-Heard it?
-Yes, ma'am. I'll be there.
It's true, Ms. Pammi.
When I was posted in Gadchiroli,
we used their weapons to deal with Naxals.
And we've bought stuff from them
many times in Mumbai as well,
for encounters.
They are considered
the Picassos of their business.
From Kashmir to Kanyakumari,
their weapons are used by everyone.
But not in Maharashtra…
We had an understanding with them.
If they don't sell their guns here,
we won't arrest them.
That's why they haven't
been nabbed before…
They still wouldn't
have been nabbed…
But their guns turned up
in UP at some minister's murder case.
Since the governments of both places
are from the same party,
we had to do it our way.
Dad! Police!
Run!
I can't testify against them.
I don't want you to.
Then?
Madam, we are very ordinary people…
Have some mercy, please.
Whatever we have earned
in this business, you can take it all!
You'll bribe me?
No, madam… Think of it as a gift.
Oh! How much will you give me as a gift?
We have saved three lakhs,
madam… Take it all!
With three lakhs, we won't even be able
to buy peanuts for the whole station.
What about crores?
At least three crores of rupees
is transported by a car,
every night.
The driver is from our village.
He made the plan.
It's a risky job, Ms. Pammi.
That it is…
Did you arrange your money?
So then, do it…
The arrangement!
There's fish… The river…
Throw in the bait and reel it in,
fucking hell!
One crore is yours,
the rest is ours…
Weapons?
You'll get them.
I'm giving you twenty four hours.
Two of you will go,
the third will stay here, as a guarantee.
Which two?
MUMBAI POLICE
He's a very old friend of ours…
We all came to Mumbai together.
Who is it at this hour…
Brother, you?
Is everything okay?
There's no danger…
Between Navi Mumbai and Panvel,
the old Khandala road stretches five
to six kilometers… Completely deserted.
You have to come and kill
two guards, that's it!
Three to four crores
in three to four minutes!
When do you want to do it?
Tonight.
Tonight won't be possible…
I took leave yesterday
for the whole week…
So call them and cancel it.
But then those fucking cops
will come catch me first…
S-Sorry, madam…
You too, sir.
It has to happen tonight, Mamu…
Think of another way.
There is one…
If… I get called in for some reason.
How will that happen?
If the driver on duty doesn't show up,
then they will have to call me…
But why won't he show up?
In that lane… Two left,
then one right then two more left…
In the yellow-colored building,
ask anyone for Ganesh.
Send his photo on WhatsApp.
Yes. Photo.
I'll forward it to you.
No, everyone.
Should I make a group?
It will be easy…
What should I name it?
Name it Peanuts!
Yes… Peanuts.
Do you spell that
as "peenuts" or "peanuts"?
Peanuts.
I thought so too.
Did you?
Now, come on.
He's gone to meet his relatives…
In Kalva…
Why isn't he answering his phone?
His phone fell
in the toilet last night.
-This one.
-That's okay!
It's ruined.
He'll go get it fixed today…
But what happened, madam?
Why are you looking for Ganesh?
Just an inquiry…
Hello.
Ma'am, he's in the next lane.
Come quick.
Okay.
Fine.
Inform Ganesh.
Yes.
Take one each.
Deliver it to the right place…
And count the money properly
and get it back…
If there's even a rupee missing
I'll cut it out of your ass!
-Make timely delivery--
-Ganesh?
Run!
What the…
Stop.
Doomed, I am doomed
We haven't done anything.
The boy's crazy,
And the girl's lovely
Walking down the aisle,
But there's trouble brewing
I was happy alone, I wonder
What made me wish for a wife
Doomed, I am doomed
Stop! Stop!
Ganesh, stop!
You will regret it
when I catch up with you.
Move. Move.
Madam, I'll need only a minute.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Let me…
I just opened the shop.
Please go someplace else.
-Just these two hairs…
-I just opened the shop.
-This one.
-Please go someplace else.
I was happy alone,
I wonder what made me wish for a wife
Doomed, I am doomed
Ganesh!
We just want to talk… Come down…
Trust me…
-No, sir.
-Come down.
Come down. Trust me.
Asshole.
Honestly… just come down.
-This is in your interest.
-No, madam.
Come down.
Ganesh…
Mamu.
Ganesh!
You idiot!
Make that WhatsApp group now, you fucker.
More sauce.
Hold this.
Hello.
Yes.
Yes. No, I'll be there on time.
They called me to work.
Ms. Pammi.
Can I ask you a question
if you don't mind?
Ask away, Paaji.
Why are you doing this?
For one good stretch, Paaji.
Good stretch?
Have you seen the size
of our staff quarters?
The size of a matchbox.
And look at me.
When I stretch, my head hits the ceiling.
So, I've seen a nice plot in Lonavala.
Great. Where?
The guy that writes songs for films.
Right behind his bungalow.
Which lyricist?
The guy that wrote, "The way
I felt when I saw a girl…"
Javed Akhtar…
-Yes, Mamu?
-Some fuckers ambushed us!
They are heading towards you.
Stop them.
Fuck!
Paaji!
Shoot them, Paaji.
Get the glass cutter.
Danny! Danny, wake up!
Fuck!
Paaji!
I'm checking!
Lovely?
Who is Lovely?
Lovely Khobre.
Narayan Khobre's daughter, Lovely Khobre?
What the fuck is she doing here?
Shall I shoot her?
Have you lost your mind, Paaji?
Khobre will burn down the whole of Mumbai.
Give it to me.
Lovely!
Who is it?
It's me, Paaji… Your father's friend.
What are you doing here?
Come out, I will explain everything.
What do you take me for?
If I come out, you'll shoot me.
Darling, I can shoot you inside as well.
Come out… Nothing will happen.
Lovely.
How did you end up here?
Shut up.
Lower the weapon.
You guys first.
When your father
used to work in Byculla,
I used to feed you in my arms.
Had I not been there, he would've lost
his head along with his legs.
Now put it down…
Down!
-Take it down.
-Left or right?
Take it down!
I am.
Paaji?
Paaji, stop!
Paaji, stop shooting.
It's me, Gopal.
Paaji, what the fuck are you doing here?
You tell us, motherfucker!
How did you come here?
Jai Hind,  Mr. Madam.
You too?
Lovely?
What are you doing here?
Danny, you…
You two are…
Holy shit…
And who are these two?
They are with us.
Us?
You are all together?
Mr. Madam…
There's three crores in the van…
Let's split it equally.
We'll have to discuss it.
Us too…
Fine…
I'll count to five.
At five, we all will throw
our weapons there…
Okay?
One…
Two…
Three…
Four…
Five!
Fuck… There's no decency left
in this world. You are all dogs!
I'll count one more time…
Be sincere and drop them.
One…
Two…
Three…
Four…
Five!
Fucking idiots…
Who should I kill first?
There is only one God!
Now your soul will leave
from your ass towards the Grim Reaper…
Jai Hind,  Mr. Madam…
Fucking hell! Look.
Paaji?
You can't even take a joke?
Unbelievable…
I mean it…
Look…
There goes my gun. Look.
Really… I was joking…
Paaji.
Hide in there.
Take your guns.
Here, take it!
-Here!
-Come on!
Assholes. Where the fuck is my gun?
Laxmi!
You know them?
I can make a deal with them.
Are you crazy? We're police…
They'll kill us right here, fucker!
He's right…
I won't tell them you're a cop.
And me?
I'll make them forgive it.
And if they don't?
Then strip!
Come out if you're still alive.
Ms. Laxmi!
Shankar.
Sardar?
What are you doing here?
What happened here?
He's selling us out.
He'll die but he won't betray us.
Ask the rest of them to come out.
Come out, everyone.
Leave your weapons.
Now leave.
I'm letting you go because of Paaji…
Otherwise, I would
have buried you alive.
Paaji.
Ms. Pammi.
I am with them from today.
The earthy scent of blood…
The air is filled
With the aroma of blood
The earthy scent of blood…
The air is filled
With the aroma of blood
It flows out of the heart
And into the earth…
The heart is hollow
Completely hollow
Not a soul in sight
Tears of blood trickling down the cheeks…
The earthy scent of blood…
The air is filled
With the aroma of blood
The lava of greed…
Is a call of death
The ego is barking out aloud…
Listen! Listen! Listen!
It's loud and clear
Loud and clear
Dishonesty is your character
Your only business is crime
Your soul is selling for a dime
The earthy scent of blood…
The air is filled
With the aroma of blood
This aroma will spread far and wide
Each soul will tremble
Each body will reek
The earthy scent of blood…
Mr. Madam, what are you doing?
D-Don't…
Mr. Madam, we'll come up with a story.
Together, we killed these Naxals.
We'll split the money halfway.
And we'll get a medal of honor.
What will you get from killing me?
You'll be dead too.
What is your logic?
Fuck the logic…
Mr. Madam, no.
This is my character!
Sonata Bar and Restaurant…
Deshpande was throwing a party
for his son passing his exams…
We had food and were going to Lonavala…
For a long drive...
And on the way,
the encounter happened…
Khobre's gang…
The van driver was working with them…
They had already killed
the security officers
and the loaders before we reached…
We challenged them…
And within a few minutes
we had them under control…
But I don't know
how the Naxals ended up there.
We tried to tackle them,
but couldn't keep up
with their weapons…
Everyone was killed…
Only Paaji, Ms. Poonam and I were alive.
With the van and the money,
they were taking us to their hideout…
I saw an opportunity,
and without thinking too much,
I attacked the driver…
The van went out of control
and started rolling down the hill…
It went and crashed
into the abandoned fort's wall… Boom!
Half of the Naxals were killed
in the accident…
But we didn't know that their leader,
Laxmi, was still alive…
She used her last bullet
to shoot Paaji right in the head.
Then she used a grenade to attack us.
At the last moment, Mr. Madam
pushed me out of the blast radius…
Guards, arms!
I'm alive only thanks to Mr. Madam.
Fire.
She deserves this medal.
All of this is because of Ms. Pammi--
Sorry, Mr. Madam's sacrifice.
Every breath I take will forever
be in her debt…
We are all proud of you…
Thank you, sir.
Cunning eyes
Your cunning eyes
Like shards of glass…
THE FROG AND THE SCORPION
Cunning eyes
Your cunning eyes
Like shards of glass…
Cunning eyes
Your cunning eyes
Like shards of glass…
Cunning eyes
Your cunning eyes
Like shards of glass…
Rob me in broad daylight
Those black eyes loot me clean
There is no escaping them
Greetings.
I hope you all ended the festive season
of Diwali with joy and new hope.
Today I'll be speaking to you
about some critical issues…
To break the grip of corruption
and black money,
an important step needs to be taken.
From midnight tonight,
that is 8th November, 2016, at 12am,
the five hundred and thousand rupee
currency notes presently in use
will no longer be legal tender.
-Five hundred…
-Bijju.
and thousand rupee currency notes…
What benefit did you get
out of this, sir?
-Papa, what happened?
-…transactions will not be acceptable.
Five hundred and thousand rupee notes,
hoarded by anti-national
and anti-social elements…
What's the logic, sir?
…will become just
worthless pieces of paper.
These good-for-nothing stray dogs
Bequeathed with an appetite for poverty
Amass the slurs of their age as capital
And each rebuff from their world as wage
No rest at night nor relief at dawn
Live in filth, dwell in drains
Should they disagree,
Turn them against each other
Just throw them a scrap of bread
They, who endure
The boot-lash of each person
Are condemned to perish
If they ever raise their heads
Humankind would regret this disdain
Should they desire to rule the world,
They could
And chew upon the very bones
Of their masters
If only they were cautioned
Of their poverty
O! For someone to tug
On their inanimate tails...